# **Seth Kalback**

74 Portland Ave, Dover NH skalback@gmail.com 603-923-0111

#### **PERSONAL SUMMARY**

A highly motivated IT professional with experience in technical support and customer service. Able to apply analytical thinking, creative problem-solving and customer service concepts to IT solutions to improve user experience and drive business results.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Certificate Program, Coding Boot Camp (In progress)**

Sept 2020 – Present University of New Hampshire | Durham, NH

#### **Bachelor of Arts, History (Incomplete)**

Sept. 2011 - 2015 Southern New Hampshire University | Manchester, NH

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Client Care Specialist II**

Cognia, Dover, NH, March 2015 - Present

- Field calls and emails regarding various test administrations as well Cognia proprietary applications.
- Train and support new team members on various test processes, applications, and standards.
- Create and maintain training documents.
- Responsible for supporting a total five applications under six different contracts.
- Document requests and customer interactions in ServiceNow and Salesforce.
- Research, analyze and troubleshoot new system issues, provide support for known, documented problems and escalate issues as needed.
- Explain solutions to technical issues to customers in a non-technical, easy-to-understand manner.

### **Co-Owner**

## Portsmouth Escape Room, Portsmouth, NH, March 2015 - Present

- Design themes and build escape room games from scratch.
- Build and install 12v electronic props.
- Design, build and maintain website.
- Install and configure computer hardware, software, networks and printers, ensuring PCI compliance for credit card processing.
- Diagnose and fix escape room software issues on PC desktop and custom-built electronic devices.

## **Library Assistant**

### Berwick Public Library, Berwick, ME, September 2014 – May 2016

- Sort, shelve, relocate, and search for library materials according to Library processes and standards.
- Search standard reference materials, including on-line sources, to answer patrons' reference questions.
- Created and maintained new website for the Library.
- Provided technical assistance with printers, network and desktops, troubleshooting and fixing issues for patrons and librarians.
- Assist patrons with 3D printing software Cubify.

# **KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES**

# **Computer Skills**

- Web Design: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, node.js
- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook)
- SalesForce and ServiceNow Ticketing Systems, Fuze, Zoom, Skype
- Proficient with Google Applications (Drive, Docs, Sheets)
- Film, Photography and Music Editing Software (Adobe Premiere and Prelude, ProTools, Photoshop)

# Languages

- Native English
- Basic Spanish

#### Personal

- Passionate book collector
- Avid Traveler